{"data":[{"question":"Would you please ___ the candies among the your classmates?","a":"divide","b":"break","c":"cut","d":"separate","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Divide: if something divides, or if you divide it, it separates into two or more parts","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"Nancy ___ herself to be good at negotiating.","a":"has been proved","b":"was proved","c":"is being proved","d":"proved","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Simple past tense (Use the Simple Past to express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past) + passive voice ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"The hens ___ tens of thousands of eggs every week.","a":"lay","b":"lie","c":"lain","d":"lied","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple present tense (Use the Simple Present to express the idea that an action is repeated or usual. The action can be a habit, a hobby, a daily event, a scheduled event or something that often happens) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"I found the sentences in the article ___ smoothly.","a":"weren't read","b":"didn't read","c":"hadn't read","d":"weren't reading","answer":"2","explain":"That's right! You chose the correct response.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"After trying many times, the salesperson ___ to see the manager","a":"succeeded","b":"managed","c":"lasted","d":"won","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Manage:to succeed in doing something difficult, especially after trying very hard","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"When Robin arrived, he learned Juliet ___ for almost one hour.","a":"has set off","b":"had gone","c":"had been away","d":"had left","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Be away: used to say that someone leaves a place or person, or stays some distance from a place or person","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"When my colleague entered the lobby, she ___ him from his picture.","a":"recognized","b":"knew","c":"looked at","d":"saw","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Recognize: to know who someone is or what something is, because you have seen, heard, experienced, or learned about them in the past","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"The thermos can ___ four liters of hot water.","a":"hold","b":"fill","c":"fix","d":"take","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Hold: to have the space to contain a particular amount of something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"My feelings were ___ when she didn't accept my love.","a":"destroyed","b":"hurt","c":"harmed","d":"beaten","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Hurt: to injure yourself or someone else","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"Prices ___ slowly in the past two years.","a":"have been risen","b":"have risen","c":"have raised","d":"have been raised","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Rise: to increase in number, amount, or value","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"}]}